Contact

joao.eurico@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/joaoeurico (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Product Management
Software Development
IT Solutions

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

João Eurico Aguiar Lima

Consultor de TIC - Software Development - Agile/SCRUM - Product Ownership

Recife

Summary

Experienced IT consultant with results in transnational companies. Strong leadership and results oriented tasks. Large experience in product development process of sofisticated technoglogy solutions. Skilled Project Manager with very successful and critical projects carried through. Long experience in Primavera Project Manager courses. Project Management instructor for PP6 and MS Project. Agile project management, SCRUM/KANBAN software projects.

Especializações: Product development and sales, IT management, Project Management

Experience

Iramai Consultoria

19 years

Consultor de tecnología
January 2002 - Present (19 years)

Recife

Diretor

September 2015 - Present (5 years 4 months)

Recife

SWS Montagem

Planejamento de projetos

November 2018 - March 2019 (5 months)

ipojuca

Responsável pela linha Konica Minolta de equipamentos e software para imagens médicas

Edax Tecnologia
Diretor Comercial/Marketing
October 2016 - September 2017 (1 year)

Recife

Diretor de toda área comercial e de marketing da EDAX/Gemmius, empresa fabricante de software para gestão hospitalar com atuação em todo o Brasil

Carl Zeiss Do Brasil

Northeast Regional Sales Manager - Microscopy Division December 2012 - September 2015 (2 years 10 months) Recife

Regional Manager in charge of sales and distribution of Carl Zeiss microscopy products for biomed and materials industry

Procenge

Consultor de Produto June 2005 - November 2012 (7 years 6 months)

Pre sales engagement, presentation, product market assertion. General sales force trainning, partnership development

Elógica

Sales and Marketing Director January 2004 - March 2005 (1 year 3 months) Manage sales and marketing team at Elógica

LeadingQuest Sales Consultant 2004 - 2005 (1 year) Sales

Sena Infomática Manager Recife Branch 2003 - 2004 (1 year)

General management of the Recife Office

Fastbee

Diretor 2000 - 2003 (3 years)

Legal representative, technology director

interdotnet Diretor 2000 - 2001 (1 year) In charge of all IT infrastructure, application systems and software services. Leading a team with more thant 20 people responsible for developing and running all systema of a ISP

Interdonet do Brasil Itda 1 year

Diretor de Tecnologia 2000 - 2001 (1 year)

Montagem da equipe de infraestrutura de TI. Consolidação dos 10 provedores de acesso que formaram a Inter.Net. Reforma em todo o sistema de billing e suporte aos clientes.

Diretor de Tecnologia 2000 - 2001 (1 year)

Enhanced and made viable a pionner broadband network called ApartNet. Consolidated 10 different ISP bought by PSI Net to form Inter.Net Brazil

Inter.net do Brasil Ltda Diretor de Tecnologia 2000 - 2001 (1 year)

Netmusic
Partner Manager
January 1999 - January 2000 (1 year 1 month)

Vectra
Services manager
July 1998 - January 1999 (7 months)

Terasoft
Partner Manager
1992 - 1998 (6 years)

Moura Gerente de TI 1990 - 1991 (1 year)

Sudene
Systems Programmer
June 1985 - July 1989 (4 years 2 months)

Education

FGV

Finance, Business Administration and Management, General · (2012 - 2012)

Interdata Cursos

Instrutor de Oracle Primavera Project Manager, Project Management · (2010 - 2010)

PMP preparation course at Quality
PMBOK trained project manager, PMBOK · (2009 - 2009)

Universidade Federal de Pernambuco BS, Computer Science · (1982 - 1989)